[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Sabi) That can’t be possible?
Rounds are at 7 o'clock?
Ah...
If the professor tells you to do it now, you can do it.
Yes, I'm going down.
[Call end sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[bird chirping]
[Jaeil’s refreshing elasticity]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
Emergency?
Uh, then anesthesiology, surgery, internal medicine, and pediatrics.
Where else?
Oh, with our professor
And we will arrange for the NICU.
[Sound of door closing]
[Sound of door opening]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
[Sound of door opening]
[Nanjing’s yawn]
[Sound of door closing]
Wow
If the date has passed, throw it away.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes, teacher
(Namkyung) Ah...
The intern says he can’t do it?
But I just eat quickly
Yes, I'm going now.
[Call end sound]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Jaeil’s tired elasticity]
(Japan) It’s been a long time
Have you had dinner?
(Sabi) Of course I couldn’t eat it.
[Sound of door closing]
Oh, it's only Wednesday
Why am I so tired?
(Nanjing) Because it’s Thursday
It's Friday
(Nanjing) False
(Japan) What?
Still, I got off work a little early today.
Right?
It's only 10 o'clock
Isn’t it a miracle?
(Lee Young) Ki...
sounds like an enemy
[train horn sound effect]
[Sound effect of clock hands moving]
[Sabi’s determined breathing]
(Sabi) Okay
I'll do it first
(Japan) Yes
[Jaeil's nervous sigh]
[Call connection tone]
Teacher, this is Sabi Kim, a first year student.
Let’s start with turn notice.
Today's third section
Professor Seo Jeong-min's mother
Uterra line contract perm
OP was cleared when I checked it.
[Lee Young’s nervous sigh]
Professor Kong Gong-seon 32 weeks 0 days
She is a premium mother.
Uh, in the MFICU with Freetum Raver
It's the 5th day of hospitalization and Ritodrine...
Uh, ritodrine...
(private money) 30, 30
Ah, this is the person who continued to use 30cc.
Yes? No, did you know?
I just said 30...
[Call end sound]
(Nanjing) Surely again?
[Lee Young sighs]
from the beginning
again
[Interesting music]
At MFICU with Freetum Laver
This is the 5th day of hospitalization.
Ritodrine is 30cc.
[Nankyung clears his throat]
(Nankyung) This is Pyo Namgyeong.
I am Mrs. Turn.
thank you
Yes?
Why are you with your wife...
Ah...
Oh, wait a minute.
No. 1013, 74-year-old Obarian cancer patient
This is the second day of POD after debulking.
Yes?
Ah
As for the Cardiac marker, I...
Not sure yet...
sorry
Sorry, let's stop here
do it again from the beginning
[Call end tone]
[Sound of door opening]
(Eunwon) Huh? Manager
(Junmo) Yes, Teacher Myeong-won.
I heard you debulked an Obarian cancer patient?
I heard the surgery was very long.
- (Eunwon) I’m glad it ended well.
- (Junmo) Oh
- (Eunwon) This is it.
- (Junmo) What is it?
(Eunwon) Have some tea
(Junmo) Oh, put it here.
[Junmo clears his throat]
No, but how does one become an obstetrics fellow?
Do you even know about gynecological surgery?
(Eunwon) Annual leave below
As I took care of everything one by one,
I found out automatically.
(Junmo) Yes...
Awesome, huh?
You must be very busy just with your obstetrics schedule.
Of course, well
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Eunwon) Ah, manager.
Next time with our professors
When going to a wine bar
Can't you call me too?
I want to go there too
[lively music]
- (Junmo) Do you like Mr. Myeong to drink?
- (Eunwon) Yes
(Jeongmin) Humans accept death
[Junmo’s voice]
There are five steps
Everyone's heard it, right?
First, negative
A little while ago, they called me Daeil.
(Jaeil) I am Eom Jaeil
How many times have I said this?
Am I that insignificant?
That can't be possible
Even though it’s like this, I
You're the first idol in your major.
I guess I'm not really good at memorizing people's names.
Right, Sabiya?
[nervous music]
- Ah...
- (Jeongmin) The second is...
anger
[Sharp sound effect]
[Crackling sound effect]
(Sabi) But you
It's your patient. Why don't you know?
[lively music]
I'm not blaming you guys.
Because my plan keeps falling apart
It's because I'm suffering too
(Jeongmin) The third is
compromise
[Soft music]
[Sound of swallowing]
It's delicious
(Jeongmin) The fourth is
(Dowon) Depression, melancholy
[sigh]
[Lonely music]
Who will be at the Shilla Hotel next month?
I'm marrying a lawyer from Kim & Chang.
what am i
I guess I'll do some dressing again
[sigh]
(Namkyung) Hey, what is this bag?
Ah, pretty
(Jeongmin) The last fifth
[cell phone notification sound]
(Sabi) Huh? This is teacher Ki Eun-mi.
No way?
Aren’t we supposed to get off work?
They say there will be 4 more inductions tomorrow.
Then there are 7 in total.
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
5 today
7 tomorrow
(Lee Young) I’m the lucky seven, hey
[Lee Young laughs]
[Lost laughter]
[light music]
(Jeongmin) The last thing is acceptance
In the end, I accepted it
[Lee Young’s heartbroken laughter]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Sabi) I will do a turn notice for the first year.
[lively music]
(Dowon) That’s ‘death and dying’
That's where it came from.
(Jeongmin) Oh
But that step
There's another place that fits perfectly
(Eunmi) What is it?
(Jeongmin) The escape and flight of medical residents
(Eunmi) Ah
(Dowon) Oh, already?
It's only been 3 weeks?
(Jeongmin) That’s the problem
Those three weeks are so ambiguous.
It's not a waste to quit
Are you a man with the same affection as you?
And we're not that close yet
And the most important thing is still
(Dowon) Hmm!
- I haven't tasted my salary yet.
- (Eunmi) Ah...
(Jeongmin) As expected, Goo Do-won has good sense.
It's been a while since the symptoms appeared.
So hold on tight
How did they get in?
(Eunmi, Dowon) Yes
[Dowon takes a breath]
(Do-won) By the way, Professor
I think you really don't know anything.
(Jeongmin) I have one
No matter how much I think about this, I don't know
Why don't you want to do this?
(Dowon) What?
With the mountains
What on earth is this good?
Why don't you want to do it?
(Dowon) I’ll go first.
(Eunmi) Goodbye, Professor.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[Announcement sound]
[Lee Young yawns]
(Nanjing) Hi
Are these your dad’s clothes?
[Lee Young yawns]
(Lee Young) What is it?
Is it a coin purse?
(Namkyung) If you don’t know something, keep your mouth shut.
Hey, I bought this because I had to wait a long time.
(Lee Young) Oh, really?
(Sabi) Hello, goodbye
[Sound of running footsteps]
(Nanjing) No, where are you going?
(Sabi) To study!
This case is dystocia, number 1.
(Jeongmin) I don’t have enough power
If we want to know dystocia well, we
Criteria for whether it is active or not
It means we have to catch each other equally.
[lively music]
In order to do that
No matter who makes an earthquake
It should be possible to measure it the same way
Then go back to the beginning and see who again
Let’s define dystocia easily.
Dystocia, abnormal labor and labor process
Yes, after all
(Jeongmin) During childbirth and labor
Affecting abnormal labor
There are 3 factors
Uh...
Ah
- (Lee Young) Write...
- (Xabi) [Clears cough] Oxytocin
(Lee Young) Even though I used oxytocin...
Even though I wrote it?
[humorous music]
I used oxytocin...
(Lee Young) Ah, even though I wrote it
Oh Yiyoung, are you not going to study like this?
(Lee Young) I’m sorry
[sigh]
Next answer Namkyung Pyo
Oh, despite the oxytocin
When the baby does not come down for more than two hours
(Namkyung) Oh, and...
(privately funded) contract
Conf...
control
(Nanjing) Conf...
They say private money is a contract, right?
- Jaeil too
- (Jae-il) Yes!
(Jeongmin) Did you hear?
yes you heard
(Jeongmin) [Sighing] In this room now
Are you studying with just me and Sabi Kim?
So is it a study? extracurricular paper
(Privately funded) Tutoring...
[Knocking sound]
(Eunmi) Professor, it’s almost time for rounds.
(Jeongmin) I’ll go
The next study is prepared by Dahye and Namgyeong.
(Dahye, Namgyeong) Yes
(Japan) Thank you for your hard work
(Jeongmin) Dowon and Professor Lim Dong-ju
You went to a conference, right?
Are you coming tomorrow?
- (Lee Young) The day after tomorrow
- (Jeongmin) Oh
But isn’t Teacher Oh Yi-young going to rounds?
(Lee Young) Ah
[Interesting music]
[Lee Young’s urgent groan]
(Jeongmin) Teacher Oh Iyoung
7 sections per day
There are 7 mothers who are on their second day of sectioning.
yes, that's right
(Jeongmin) Then, during the patient presentation.
I need to tell you about the characteristics of the mother.
Wouldn't you know better who is who?
(Lee Young) Oh, yes, sorry.
(Jeongmin) And Yoon Seon-mi’s mother was at 22 weeks.
Because Reactivity doesn’t exist in the first place.
You don’t have to do NST
(Lee Young) Yes, I understand.
Oh, please recognize all of Shim Hee-young’s mothers.
[Announcement sound]
[Lee Young sighs]
[telephone dial button sound]
[Call connection tone]
Uh, teacher, this is Jongno Yulje.
Uh, I'm a first-time mother at 34 weeks and the baby is small.
I was watching
(Lee Young) Uh...
The amniotic fluid has decreased significantly and the monitor is not working well.
I think I need to go into labor.
We don't have any NICU space.
Yes? Oh, wait a minute.
Baby weighs 1.5kg
AFI is...
It's 4
Yes? Documents?
Oh, yes, I will prepare it for you.
yes, thank you, yes
[Puts down the receiver]
- (Eunwon) Teacher
- (Lee Young) Yes
The teacher
Why do you work so stupidly?
(Lee Young) Yes?
[Eunwon’s light smile]
(Eunwon) No, I’m stuttering.
You act strangely
(Lee Young) Strange?
(Eunmi) Lee Young-ah
Have all Sim Hee-young's mothers been cleared?
(Lee Young) Ah, yes, I am doing it.
(Eunmi) When I received that power request form
Take the early prenatal test results with you.
That way you don't have to do it twice
Oh yes, thank you
my words
(Eunwon) That’s what I’m saying
Teacher Oh I-young
When working
Don't just call first.
Do some thinking
Is it because your mind wanders?
There's so little passion
What did you say
(Jae-il) Hello!
[Announcement sound]
Hello, let me help you.
(Smile) Ah...
thank you
(Japan) Now, this way
The obstetrics department is here.
(Smile) I’m not pregnant.
Done
(Dahye) Yeommiso
(Jae-il) Hello.
(Dahye) You’re just in the emergency room.
You said you were feeling low
Now
Be careful
[Smile's labored groan]
[Dahye's light smile]
The professor
[sigh of smile]
He says let’s take revenge first.
They say they will catch the cancer later.
(smile) Okay
You look very unwell today.
When I got to the hospital, my condition was bad.
Can it be good?
But I'm especially more irritated today.
(Smile) Let’s go, teacher.
(Dahye) Yes
[lively music]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
(Eunpyo) If you are a doctor,
I don't think it will work
No, if you say you have a fever
Come and not even see my face
I say it's okay and leave
(Sabi) Every time the temperature is measured
You always had a fever below 37.5 degrees.
[Program operation sound effect]
During pregnancy
Progesterone concentration in the blood rises
You may feel like you have a fever
Also, the mother
Isn’t this the type of person that gets very hot?
I think about it
Yes?
What?
(Eunpyo) Ha, it’s ridiculous, really.
Is that what you want to do now?
I don't get hot
And the heat and fever
I'm not so stupid that I can't tell the difference.
No, then what about disinfection?
Stayed in the hospital for 4 weeks
This is the first time I've felt sick while disinfecting.
Come and stab me without saying a word
I said it hurts
- What?
- That's...
Because I can't help it
Look, look, professor, did you hear this?
(Eunpyo) I heard you said exactly that?
(Kisun) Ah, yes
(Eunpyo) No, to the mother who said she was sick.
It's a deal that can't be helped.
That's it now
Is this what a doctor would say to a pregnant woman?
Mom, I'm being sensitive even though I'm like this, huh?
To such an insincere person
How do you have a baby?
Professor, I've never done anything like this before.
There wasn't one, right?
sorry
It must have been very uncomfortable.
I will make sure this doesn't happen again in the future.
[Eunpyo’s sigh]
(Eunpyo) Professor
A person like that
Aren’t you supposed to be a doctor?
[Program operation sound effect]
[humorous music]
[Kiseon’s embarrassed sigh]
(Kiseon) Yes, how did something like this happen?
Take some rest
[Sound of curtain hitting]
[Program operation sound effect]
(Kisun) Do you want me to be big?
Do you want to have surgery or have a baby?
Don't crash, just do what you're told
They tell you to do it right, but is it that difficult?
[Sigh of the steamer]
Go and apologize, you were wrong.
I
In medical facts
I don't think there's anything wrong or wrong.
So what did that mother do wrong?
I did something wrong and can't even eat
You can't even sleep!
[Sigh of the steamer]
I'm not asking you to apologize because you did something wrong.
(Kisun) An apology of consolation or not
Made with consideration and empathy
Something like an apple, huh? There is such a thing.
Then it's not an apology
Once again, explain the situation in detail
Let me explain
Oh, just go and apologize!
[Interesting music]
(Kiseon) Why can’t you understand what I’m saying?
They said they were moving to the hospital.
If the mother is transferred to the hospital like that,
all the people
Do you blame me or do you blame me?
I'll have a good talk with the mother.
I will solve it
yes
do anything
Do anything to solve it
(Sabi) Yes
Isn’t it Teacher Kim Sa-bi’s F?
yes?
(Kisun) I don’t think it’s F.
I'm a straight A, right?
[Humorous sound effects]
[humorous music]
(Kiseon) T yes
capital letter T
(Jaehwi) Meal, yes
How are you feeling?
First of all, the numbers have improved a lot.
Ah, yes
(Jaehwi) And you started exercising, right?
(Patient 1) No
yet
As I said yesterday, exercise
You have to keep doing it a lot to get better.
(Jaehwi) So, walk often.
(Patient 1) Oh, but I’m so hungry.
I can't move
(Jaehwi) No, Sik...
From this morning?
Oh, I guess that meal was taken out?
[Jaeil’s surprised exclamation]
(Dahye) Oh, you didn’t give me food, right?
Oh, sorry.
- I'll prepare it so you can eat right away.
- (Jaehwi) Yes
For no reason, you spend a few hours because of us.
Did you have a harder time?
Isn’t it okay to do this?
[Dahye's awkward laughter]
I'm so sorry
- Let’s have some water first.
- (Dahye) Yes
(Jaehwi) Please drink some water first.
[Heavy sound effect]
[Meaningful music]
[Sound of door closing]
[Typewriter sound effect]
[Keyboard operation sound]
sorry for me
(Nanjing) I will do the same.
So, why are you saying such useless nonsense?
Are you being filmed by a patient?
[Nanjing’s sigh]
It's not a motive, it's something, something
Today's fortune
They say unexpected enemies can arise.
It was you
sorry
But Namkyung
Me, without Teacher Dahye’s knowledge
I think I could work in the ward.
- How come I'm the only one who doesn't do anything?
- Don't do it.
(Namkyung) If you get caught
By then, I'm out too.
You, you're just stuck in the operating room.
I'm just arranging the operating room.
I hope it won't cause an accident
(Eunmi) Namgyeong, have you eaten?
- Jae-il couldn’t eat either, right?
- (Residing in Japan) Yes
I left a packed lunch in the duty room.
Do you want to eat now?
- (Jae-il) Uh, yes
- (Nanjing) Later.
(Eunmi) Baby, eat now, you must be hungry.
[Nankyung’s embarrassed laughter]
(Nanjing) Yes
Be sure to eat it
Oh, I'm on my way to buy coffee.
Shall I buy you coffee? What do you like?
- (Jae-il) Ah...
- (Nanjing) I will eat later.
I don't have time right now
(Eunmi) Okay
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Japan) Wow...
As expected, Eunmi Teresa
Namgyeong, you are good...
I want to eat too, I want to eat too
But you don't have time to eat, right?
[humorous music]
(Nanjing) When will you prepare for tomorrow’s rounds?
When do you do dressing again?
[Sighing] Tomorrow, Professor Jaehwi Ryu.
9 surgeries alone
But they said there was another patient in the intensive care unit.
A whole day goes by just with dressing.
They said they were bringing up another patient.
Plus, that patient with a sad smile that you hit with an accident.
They say it's not a joke
What?
Because the 4-person room is uncomfortable
I moved to a single room.
The window in the next room is bigger
He asked me to change it
[Jaeil’s surprised gasp]
wow
(Nanjing) And dressing a day...
(Smile) Over there
Only two dressings today
You didn't do it?
(Namkyung) Oh, you are Yeommiso, right?
yes
(Namkyung) Oh, I just took over.
four times a day
You know?
Ah, yes
(Smile) And on cleanliness
Please pay close attention
Yes?
yes
[humorous music]
Shall I bring you a lunch box?
I don't have time to eat
(Jaeil) Oh, that’s right, that’s right
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[A siren is heard in the distance]
Do you listen to music?
So what do you listen to?
What, do you hear, nya, go?
yes sorry
(Lee Young) Yes
[Call end sound]
What are you listening to?
I swear
(Jay) Ah...
I guess he hates me so much
Teacher Myeong-won?
The nurses say that
They say it's famous for disciplining first-year students.
(Lee Young) Childishly
Ah, why are you holding the military discipline? mesna magazine
Also, I heard you're more sensitive this year?
why?
(Japan) Professor Lim Dong-ju is retiring next year.
I can get a spot
Hey, that's why they moved to this hospital
I absolutely hate the years below.
What happens among professors?
I think it has pretty good reviews.
They say there is a high possibility of becoming a professor.
Ah!
Ah, if only I were a real professor.
Our second year won’t be easy either.
I wish you good luck
What, what's wrong?
(Jaeil) Play a song
- There is a good idol called Hiboyz.
- (Lee Young) I hate it.
(Jaeil) Ah, why?
[Sunwoo Jung-ah’s ‘Let’s Run Away’ plays]
[sigh]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Lee Young) Yes, teacher
Yes?
[nervous music]
[Lee Young’s urgent groan]
(Japan) Hey
(Lee Young) Oh, teacher, I’m really sorry.
I am a mother with a myomectomy history.
Suddenly active raver
It happens every 2 minutes.
I think I need to have emergency sex.
(Sanghyun) Yes? Now?
There really isn't an operating room.
Oh, not even if I die
(Lee Young) Oh, it has to be there.
Please open one room quickly.
If there is a room where the surgery is completed
I'll go and sort it out.
Oh, please just this once, sir.
[Lee Young’s embarrassed exclamation]
(Sanghyun) I’ll push down soon.
[Sanghyun sighs]
Do you know that mountains are like the real Grim Reaper?
[Sound of door closing]
Ah, just getting a phone call gives me goosebumps, it's just that
(Lee Young) I’m sorry
Suddenly, the contractions became 2 minutes apart.
(Sanghyun) I also have a child.
I roughly know what you’re feeling.
Oh, it's not a lie
There was no real operating room.
I'm glad the surgery here was over quickly.
(Lee Young) Thank you
[Call connection tone]
(Lee Young) Ah, teacher
I will drop the baby off at the ward.
(Eunwon) Uh, I’ll get off the delivery.
You keep it there, make sure
(Lee Young) Ah, yes
[Call end sound]
(Sanghyun) Oh, why don’t you come down like this?
They said it was urgent so they held off on the surgery afterwards?
(Lee Young) I’ll call you again.
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Eunwon) If surgery is suddenly decided
[Call end sound]
It's not easy to give birth on time.
[Interesting music]
Besides, it's nighttime and it's hard to find time to do the surgery.
It's almost impossible in obstetrics.
If your daughter becomes president, I will also have a part to play, right?
[Sangmi’s laughter]
(Sangmi) Oh, of course
- (Lee Young) Labor pain for the mother...
- (Eunwon) Oh, you worked hard.
Professors waste so much time
Please don't guess
(Sangmi) Oh, that’s right, teacher.
I will definitely remember
(Eunwon) If you send your friends to my outpatient clinic,
I will treat you well
[Sangmi’s light smile]
[Sound of door opening]
(Sangmi) Yes, thank you
(Eunwon) Anesthesiologist
I hope you take care of me today
(Sanghyun) Teacher
- But I heard it was a huge emergency.
- (Eunwon) Yes?
I know what you mean...
What happened?
(Lee Young) When you were talking to me on the phone earlier
(Eunwon) Currency?
Uh, you talked to me on the phone.
Why is that?
Uh...
Ah, teacher
I would like PCA to be Epidural.
(Sanghyun) [Sighing] Put in the epidural catheter.
It takes 20 to 30 minutes to be anesthetized, really.
First-year teacher, isn’t this a bit much?
Even lying to other departments
Should I do it like this?
- (Lee Young) Oh, that’s not it...
- (Sanghyun) It’s okay.
Oh, what are you saying to the professor?
Oh, it sucks, really, Mr.
[Lee Young sighs]
[Program operation sound effect]
[humorous music]
It's the first meal I've had in a few days.
Don't disturb me
I told you to be considerate.
That's right, considerate
[Sound effect of clock hands moving]
[Program operation sound effect]
It's already 10 o'clock
Insomnia is bad for the fetus.
This is empathy
Empathize with the mother's heart
Uh...
[Program operation sound effect]
[alarm sound]
[depressing music]
(Namkyung) Oh, I was planning to shower today.
Oh, I don't know, oh, I don't know, I don't know
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[Sound of door closing]
[Sound effect of clock hands moving]
[bird chirping]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
[Lee Young sighs]
[camera shutter sound]
[Sighing] I really can’t do this, Mr.
[Knocking sound]
[Hymn music plays]
(Namkyung) Yeommiso, are you okay?
I'll do the dressing
(Smile) Did you wash your hands?
Yes, I washed it.
(Smile) Wait a minute
(Namkyung) Yes?
Could you please change my gloves?
Uh, did you just put this on?
I would like you to change the tweezers as well.
(Namkyung) Uh...
yes
[Sound of taking off gloves]
I do it twice in the morning and twice in the afternoon.
You know there are a total of four, right?
It was delivered
Please be sure to stick to the designated time.
Please
yes
(Nanjing) I will take off the tape.
It stings
Eom Jae-il...
[Interesting sound effects]
(Residence in Japan) Huh? teacher
Patient Park Ga-young has disappeared.
I have surgery today.
(Dahye) Ah, that patient Park Gayoung
With a sist rupture at dawn
The pain was so severe that I had surgery right away.
Didn't I tell you?
You are in the intensive care unit now.
- Oh, then I'm in the intensive care unit...
- You don't have to.
Teacher, please take a break.
I'll contact you when something happens.
(Residence in Japan) No...
[Jaeil’s sigh]
I liked patient Park Ga-young.
They told me to come in for surgery.
(Major) Wait a minute
[Sound of busy conversation between medical staff]
(Nurse 1) Teacher, wait a minute.
Where is Teacher Kim Sa-bi?
Where is he?
(Jeongmin) There’s a conference, don’t be late and come
[Sound of door opening]
(Kiseon) I
Definitely yesterday, huh?
I told you to go talk to me yesterday.
I went
Because you are eating
I went there at night too.
(Sabi) You need to sleep well at night
At the level of empathy and consideration
Hey!
[Sigh of the steamer]
The mother is right.
Mr. Sabi Kim
Can you become a doctor like that?
(Kiseon) I can’t empathize, I can’t even get the timing right.
Moreover, they cannot read the signals sent by the mother.
So it will be resolved soon
That's how big it gets!
[The frustrating elasticity of the steamer]
I don't know, I'll figure it out somehow
Solve it no matter what, okay?
Solve it right now, okay?
I can't stand it anymore
This
Last warning, huh?
[Kiseon’s irritated sigh]
[Sad music]
[Sabi’s sobbing]
(Sabi) What should I do...
(Sora) Well, today is General, right?
(Lee Young) Yes, I’m General.
(Sora) Sanghyun, check, twice
Are you done fasting?
(Lee Young) Yes, I am fasting.
(Sora) Sanghyeonah
Did you check it?
Did you ask the mother?
(Sanghyun) Yes, I did it.
(Sora) Operability is
I'll check
[Call connection tone]
Uh, Eunwon.
Has all operability been resolved?
Okay
[Call end sound]
(Mugang) There is no indication for this surgery.
Didn’t you decide not to go to pediatrics?
(Lee Young) Teacher Myungwon Myeongwon
You said you needed it
(Mu-gang) Ah...
But is it really bad for the baby?
Can I trust you?
- (Lee Young) Yes?
- (Mugang) No, they always say it’s bad.
Everything will be fine once it comes out.
I had some doubts about a few things before this, right?
(Lee Young) What are you talking about before?
(Mugang) There were many things.
Rather than just saying something,
If the baby has a problem
I thought they were calling us to blame us.
(Lee Young) What?
(Mugang) Ah, our pediatrician.
You know there's really no one there.
So, from now on, each other
Let's not lie, well...
That's what I mean
[Lee Young sighs]
[Sound of door opening]
(Eunwon) Hello, goodbye
[Interesting music]
(Sanghyeon) Hello?
(Eunwon) What should I do, because of us again?
I can't even eat lunch, I'm sorry.
Our first year, no accidents today
Everyone is having a hard time like this.
[Lee Young sighs]
(Main lead) Teacher
Patient No. 1013, Jeonghye Yoo
It's my second day on POD and I have a slight fever.
This is going to be released as a fever reducer. Has it been confirmed?
[Keyboard operation sound]
(Nanjing) Yes
(main role) and
No. 1016 Kim Seon-ah is a professor.
WBC count is too high
He asked me to go for an ESR and CRP test.
Oh, I'll do the charting first.
There are only 20 overdue charts.
(Juyeon) Yes
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, Teacher Ki Eun-mi.
(Eunmi) Uh, Namgyeong
We just went to the restaurant for a moment.
It's okay
(Namkyung) I’m behind on work.
Can’t I eat it later?
yes
[Call end sound]
[Nanjing’s light sigh]
and
[sigh]
(Main role) Single room patient Yeommiso
It's dressing time
[Nanjing’s tired sigh]
[humorous music]
If it's late, like before
I think it's going to be a mess, teacher.
(Namkyung) Oh, it’s really unusual.
They say my hands are so dirty
Why do you ask me to dress you up?
I'm good at dressing
It’s not like the disease is going away.
Why are you so obsessed?
Haha, I hate it so much I'm dying
What's wrong with smiling, always crying...
[Sad music]
Teacher Juyeon
(Juyeon) Yes
Please call the intern teacher.
Are you an intern teacher?
A patient with a bright smile ahead
I don't think I can dress
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Mugang) Oh, that was a bit too much.
(Sanghyun) That’s right
What would you do to a first year student like that?
I don't think so...
(Mugang) That’s right.
[A siren is heard]
(Japan) Wow
[cell phone ringing sound]
Fifth ambulance arrives
No, there won't be enough people in the ER?
(Sanghyun) Yes, yes, I’m leaving now.
[cell phone ringing sound]
yes
(Mugang) Uh, Teacher Eom.
There is a huge shortage of pediatrics
Yes, 30 seconds.
(Jae-il) Please go in.
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, Teacher Dahye.
I requested that the CT scan you requested was urgent.
Uh, I checked in to operating room number 11.
I called the surgery.
Shall we go straight into that operating room?
(Dahye) Oh, no, no
I'll finish with the intern here.
Ah... yes
Then you don't need me?
(Dahye) Ah, yes, yes
(Nurse 2) Teacher Dahye!
(Dahye) Yes, let’s go!
I'm leaving work today, I worked hard.
[Call end sound]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[light music]
(Sabi) Since I was born
It was my first time getting scolded, but
Is this the film you guys are talking about?
ugly fur
Is that it?
(Lee Young) That’s right
I really like Professor Seo Jeong-min.
(Sabi) That’s why I came to the obstetrics department.
You must have been very disappointed in me this time, right?
What should I do?
Well, what am I
Others tell me
Because I’m not disappointed once or twice
I don't think it'll be okay
(Lee Young) You don’t know
[Mouse operation sound]
The mother said so
People like me shouldn't be doctors
You're just talking nonsense
like me
Oh I-young
A person like me really
Should I not be a doctor?
I'm not qualified to be a doctor, right?
Stop?
Are you planning to quit being a doctor?
when?
I'm going to endure it one more time and quit
[Program operation sound effect]
[humorous music]
(Sabi) No
What am I going to do?
I want to be a doctor!
Do it
you want to do it
[Program operation sound effect]
Is that so?
Then shall I do it?
[Program operation sound effect]
Uh, do it
Then I'll go and see the mother one more time. I'm leaving.
[Sound of door opening and closing]
(Lee Young) Wow...
He's a bit of a jerk too.
[sigh]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[cell phone ringing sound]
[Lee Young sighs]
Uh, I'm going into surgery now.
People having surgery tomorrow
Please take my research consent form.
Also... yo?
(Eunwon) Huh? what?
hello?
yes, i understand
(Eunwon) Oh, and today in the morning
You didn’t send it?
yes?
I mean the photo
What, are you giving up already?
Just a few days?
I sent it now, I forgot.
[snort]
You really forgot, right?
Lying is also a habit
[nervous music]
(Eunwon) You have to develop good habits from the beginning.
And if you want to do it here, you can do it.
If you don't want to do it, don't do it
It's not teacher Oh I-young's house.
It's a social life, so that doesn't work.
This is all for teacher Oh I-young
That's why
[Call end sound]
[snort]
How
Do you even know how to flutter?
what?
What will we do next?
It's crazy
How dare you
[Eunwon’s tired moans]
(Lee Young), I don’t have any money.
Do you have no temper?
Sir, I won't do it.
I originally didn’t want to do it either, right?
[Emergency broadcast sound]
(Announcement) Obstetrics and Gynecology Code Blue
[nervous music]
Obstetrics and Gynecology Code Blue on the first basement level of the main building
Are you a cancer patient?
No way
Maternal CPR?
(Lee Young) Everyone on duty went into surgery?
(Announcement) Obstetrics and Gynecology Code Blue
Main building basement 1st floor...
(Lee Young) Oh, there’s no one.
Mistress
IC
Wow! Why don't you accept it?
[Call connection tone]
[Jeongmin’s urgent breathing]
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
(Jeongmin) Please get out of the way, this is the obstetrics and gynecology department.
Is the mother okay?
(Doctor) I'll change hands, one, two, three
Professor Gong Gong-seon said the surgery was almost complete.
I arranged it for the room next door.
(Lee Young) Come over as soon as you’re done.
They say you’re doing a section.
(Junseok) I will transport the patient.
(Lee Young) Uh, I’ll change hands.
one, two, three
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
(Junseok) Please raise your head.
(Jeongmin) Now, be careful.
(Junseok) One, two, three
- (Jeongmin) Please do CPR right away.
- (Junseok) Yes
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
(Eunwon) Wait a minute
What happened?
(Jeongmin) Well done, go, hurry up
(Lee Young) Oh, me?
(Jeongmin) There’s no help in that room, hurry!
(Lee Young) Ah, yes
[Sound of running footsteps]
Professor, are you here?
Are you on duty today?
Ah... yes
But why aren't you answering the phone?
That surgery...
[Jeongmin sighs]
(Jeongmin) Yes
But which room?
I was in the operating room too?
Ah...
That...
(Eunwon) That...
I was preparing for surgery, but it was canceled, so I took a short break.
sorry
What is there to be sorry about?
Did you lie?
Or even if the obstetrics and gynecology department showed CPR.
I was so confused that I came out late!
(Eunwon) That...
You don't have to answer
Because we won't have anything to do in the future.
[Eunwon’s trembling breathing]
(Kiseon) Teacher Oh I-young is amazing, huh?
I'm not embarrassed that it's been a year
How are you so calm?
Thanks to you, mother and baby survived.
Good job, really
(Lee Young) Thank you
(Kiseon) Today, tomorrow
Check the mother’s vitals carefully.
(Lee Young) Yes
Tomorrow?
Ah
sorry
Tomorrow?
I... do it?
(Kiseon) Then who does it?
It's me
(Kiseon) Teacher Oh I-young
Still, it's better than Teacher Kim Sa-bi, yes.
mountains and sun
When I come to the mountains, I...
It's okay
(Lee Young) Oh, that’s not it
I said it was okay because it was really okay.
[humorous music]
Well then bye
[Sigh of the steamer]
(Kisun) He or she
[Sound of door opening]
[sound of a switch being pressed]
[Sound of door closing]
(Nanjing) What is it?
Are you here already?
Ah... haven't you gone yet?
(Lee Young) No
[Sad music]
I couldn't go
But today definitely
Going
(Nankyung) What kind of baggage is this?
If anyone sees me, they will think I'm running away.
You know, me over there...
(Nanjing) Later, later
I wasn't even prepared for rounds.
Ah
I didn't see the x-ray, but I'm in big trouble.
Ah, the dressing.
When do you finish dressing?
Hey...
[Sound of door closing]
I went to talk, but he told me not to come in.
(Sabi) Don’t tell me anything
I really can't do it
[Knocking sound]
[Sound of door opening]
Eom Jae-il, the kids' condition right now...
Good morning
- (Lee Young) Hello
- (Dowon) Hello
- (Sabi) Hello?
- (Dowon) Hello, goodbye
(Namkyung) Hello?
What about breakfast?
(Nanjing) I’m hungry
But I have to go
(Dowon) I brought you a hamburger.
Don't eat...
-What is going on...
- (Lee Young) I will eat well.
[Humorous sound effects]
[Calm music plays]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Residence in Japan) I...
yes
Even if it exists, it’s a nuisance.
It's not helpful and I don't need it.
It's better without it
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Jaeil’s surprised groan]
(Jae-il) I’m not running away, I’m late.
I'm on my way now
(Dahye) What?
teacher?
[Jaeil's urgent groan]
Teacher, can you hear me?
Yes, sir, I can hear you well.
I'm not running away, I...
(Dahye) Today’s surgery lasts 5 hours.
There's nothing to take care of in the meantime.
Because I have nothing to take care of
In the meantime, I'm keeping my eyes closed.
[Call end sound]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
(Jaeil) You don’t know, I ran away
[Interesting music]
- (Junmo) Pyo Nam-kyung
- (Nanjing) Yes?
(Junmo) You have a hamburger now
Does it catch your eye? uh?
Why do patients keep using dressings?
Complaint?
- That's...
- (Junmo) What!
Oh, sorry.
(Junmo) I wonder if he’s good at that one thing
What's wrong?
There are only a few patients, tsk.
[humorous music]
[Nankyung sighs in frustration]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Main lead) Teacher
A lot of patients are looking for Yeommiso’s single room.
It's past dressing time
Me?
[sigh]
Can’t I go to another teacher?
(Juyeon) Ah, yesterday too
The intern teacher came
You were very angry.
He said he would definitely get it from the teacher.
What should I do?
[sigh]
[Nanjing’s light sigh]
Don't press it
(Smile) Please make it as painless as possible.
[humorous music]
(Nanjing) Yes
Well, I made a mistake yesterday...
sorry
In the future, another teacher will come...
no
Teacher, please keep doing it.
- (Nanjing) Yes?
- (Smile) 4 times a day like now
If you can't do it
I'll tell the professor
(Nanjing) Uh, no, no.
I will come
[Nankyung’s awkward laughter]
[Crying sound]
[Sabi’s crying sound]
(Sabi) Professor Gong Gong-seon
I scream and tell them to get out
Professor Seo Jeong-min
don't even look at me
me
I don't think I can be a doctor
[cell phone ringing sound]
What should I do if I don’t receive it?
I'm fine, go now
no
I did everything I was told, but
(Lee Young) And anyway
I'm going
(Sabi) Oh, are you going?
Ward? Operating room?
somewhere else
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
- (Sabi) Hello?
- (Dowon) Yes
- (Lee Young) Hello
- (Dowon) They were both here.
I was already trying to call you
Sabi, I heard Eunmi was waiting for you at the restaurant?
(Sabi) Oh, that’s right
- Let's go.
- (Dowon) Enjoy your meal
And Teacher Oh I-young
Me? Why, what
Did I do everything I asked?
Yeah, so I wanted to ask you something.
(Dowon) Well, in 10 minutes
Look in front of the emergency room
[sigh]
(Dowon) I contacted everyone in Songdo.
- (Lee Young) Am I going alone?
- (Dowon) Oh
What if the baby suddenly comes out on the way?
Clamp the cord with a clip and
Just cut it with sterile scissors.
While I was on my way, Teacher Oh I-young
I'm your doctor and surgeon, okay?
[Humorous sound effects]
I'm not fooled, ah...
I'm also quick-witted
(Lee Young) If it’s that dangerous
Would you like to spend a year?
So
(Do-won) Because I checked the mother’s condition.
Don't be too nervous and go
Nothing bad will happen along the way.
Refresh yourself while you're here.
[cell phone ringing sound]
See you later
Uh, uh, I'm leaving now.
[bird chirping]
[Lee Young sighs]
(Lee Young) The weather is perfect for splashing around.
- (Lee Young) Hello?
- (Sooyoung) Hello?
Teacher, how long will it take us?
I think it will take about an hour
(Swimming) Ah...
Ah, yes
Well, if you have any inconveniences
Please tell me right away
Ah, yes, sir.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Namkyung) Yes, teacher.
(Dahye) Oh, let’s eat, right?
I'm sorry, but can you come in 10 minutes?
(Nanjing) Yes, yes, I will go now.
[Call end sound]
[Nankyung groans in frustration]
(Hye-seon) Right?
It’s Nanjing, right?
- (Namkyung) Huh?
- (Hye-seon) That’s right!
Have you been here at the hospital?
Oh, that's right, that's right, Jongno Yulje
Hey, you were eating.
Eat it quickly, eat it quickly
(Namkyung) Huh? no, no
I ate it all, I ate it all
Hyeseon, what are you doing here?
Why in the hospital?
(Hye-seon) Ah, here is the director of the health check-up center.
Because my father-in-law is a friend
To get a checkup before marriage
(Namkyung) Oh, you said you were married, right?
You must come to the wedding
Okay?
Yeah, I'll go.
Hey, but I almost didn't recognize you.
(Hye-seon) I feel like a different person
I'm a little busy
(Hye-sun) Yes...
Wait a minute
Hey, I'm up.
I'll go first
- Finish eating.
- (Namkyung) Huh?
Uh, okay, go.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
(Juyeon) Teacher Yeom Miso is a patient.
It seems like there's more ooze coming out.
Please complain
Why don't you give me painkillers?
Also the heart
They say it feels like I'm running fast.
- You should come and take a look...
- I can't go.
(Juyeon) Yes?
I said something rude
It seems like he's trying to stop me and kill me.
Because I won't go any further.
Whether you get it from someone else or do it yourself.
Please tell me to take care of it.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Nanjing) I can’t do any more
I can't, I can't
Hello?
(Article 1) Oh, yes, hello?
Where should we go?
Myeongjin Officetel
No, it's a bathroom.
no
Department store, please go to the nearest department store
Ah, yes, I understand.
Sir, please increase the audio.
(Article 1) Yes
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
[Nankyung’s sobbing sound]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Sir
Please return the car, quickly!
[Doppler operation sound]
[Heavy breathing]
I feel like my stomach is a little tight.
(Lee Young) That can’t be possible?
(Swimming) Isn’t it?
Write, but
It seems a little different from when I started.
It'll be okay, teacher?
(Lee Young) Which one are you more uncomfortable with?
(Sooyoung) Write, uh...
I think the left side is a bit lumpy.
[dark music]
Wait a minute
[Call connection tone]
- (Dowon) Hello?
- (Lee Young) Ah, teacher
We have to go for another 30 minutes.
The mother suddenly
You said you had a knot in your stomach.
How much does it hurt for the mother?
Do you feel like you need to poop?
(Lee Young) You don’t feel like that, do you?
(Swimming) Ah...
Write, ah, I don’t think so.
Well, it doesn't hurt very much.
You don’t even feel like you need to poop.
Is something like amniotic fluid flowing?
No, there isn't
(Dowon) It’s not that urgent.
Continuously check the baby's heart rate with Doppler.
Uterine contractions are okay with the manual, but watch carefully.
We reassure the mother
yes, i understand
[Call end sound]
[Sooyoung moans in pain]
[Sooyoung exhales]
[Doppler operation sound]
Driver, please hurry up a bit.
[heavy music]
- (Guidance voice) Because the customer is on the phone...
- (Nankyung) Who are you talking to right now?
[Press the elevator button repeatedly]
[Call end sound]
(Juyeon) I didn’t answer the phone so I left a message.
Please clean up line 1011.
Room 1011 is a patient suffering from miso?
Why are you suddenly organizing the lines?
[Nankyung’s heavy breathing]
(Juyeon) Where did you go?
Teacher Dowon organized the line.
He did it and left.
(Nankyung) Why suddenly...
[Guardian's crying sound]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
teacher
I'll just do that dressing once.
Yes?
(Nanjing) I couldn’t do it yesterday either.
I could only do it once today.
So I'll just do it one last time
(Smile) Then, go ahead.
But did you wash your hands?
(Namkyung) Then, wash your hands first...
[Nanjing’s surprised exclamation]
What is it?
To get my glasses
(Smile) But what if I’m an hour late?
It's oozing and my heart feels weird.
Where have you been, you were surprised!
I moved because the window next door was wider.
[Sigh of relief]
Well done
[Weeping moans]
[Nankyung’s sobbing sound]
It disappears after you control it.
[sniffling sound]
Something got in my eye
(Namkyung) But how do you know about Conta?
Even a Seodang dog knows that much in 3 years.
don't worry
I washed my hands twice today
The gloves are new too.
[sniffling sound]
Are you scolded because of me?
Or is it because you're having a hard time because of me?
It's not
It's because of me
I'm sorry if I bothered you.
Sorry to bother you
No
(Smile) That place disinfects well.
The professor said that
I’m also rubbing this medicine.
I know it's not a big deal
Receive it from someone who is good at it
I wonder if anything would be better
[Calm music]
It's been about 3 years
That's how people become
I know you're having a hard time
I
All I can think about is myself
I'm sorry
No, the dressing is important.
This isn't a big deal.
(Nanjing) If you disinfect well, the wound will heal quickly.
Discharge is also faster.
And I'm really good at it
I'm the best among our first-year students.
[light laughter]
Then will you come again tomorrow?
(Nanjing) Ojo, number 4
tomorrow is morning
I only come once in the morning, to straighten my nose
Are you discharged?
Oh, look, I was discharged sooner.
[sniffling sound]
(Smile) I guess you’re happy that I’m leaving.
Oh no, no, no
No, no?
Being discharged is the best thing.
[Nankyung’s sobbing sound]
(Namkyung) I’m really good at picking out the lines of my nose.
[Smile chuckles]
[Nanjing’s laughter]
(Article 2) Are you okay?
[Sigh of relief]
[light sigh]
- (Minha) Teacher Oh I-young?
- (Lee Young) Yes
[Minha’s light smile]
(Lee Young) Ah, hello
You are teacher Yulje from Jongno, right?
Are you there yet?
I was wondering if the mother was okay.
(Lee Young) Ah, let’s go
He kept saying it felt like he had a lump in his stomach.
I said it was okay again
I asked him to go quickly because he was sick.
Oh, the doctor at our hospital said it's okay.
[light laughter]
- Teacher Gu Do-won?
- (Lee Young) Yes
But it's been a year and this is my first time doing something like this.
I'm worried because I don't know him well.
(Minha) Mother
uterine contraction inhibitor
I think he got sick because he didn't go in well.
(Lee Young) Ah...
(Minha) Are you okay now?
It's really okay
[Sigh of relief]
Are you very surprised?
yes
If 4 years is okay,
It's really okay
And what if it's not okay?
It's the teacher's fault, right?
(Minha) Good things about first year
That's just one thing
If anything goes wrong, it’s the senior’s fault
Otherwise, is it the fault of the person who ordered it?
That's right
It's all Gudowon's fault.
(Lee Young) But even if it’s not my fault
If something wrong happens to the mother
I think it will be something I will never forget for the rest of my life.
I'll go then
(Minha) Hmm
Wait a minute, teacher.
Uh...
Would you like to go have a cup of coffee?
yes?
(Minha) Huh?
[train horn sound effect]
(Lee Young) Uh...
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
(Minha) I saw the transfer coming.
I think it’s been a great first year.
(Lee Young) Thank you
(Minha) Teachers from higher years
It’s so pretty, right?
(Lee Young) Not at all
(Minha) A
Then the seniority difference is strange.
Write...
I barely even got a residency.
I only remember being scolded for three months in the first year.
Everyone screamed like that when they saw me.
No, it's your first time, so it's natural that you don't know, right?
Why was everyone like that? It was so unfair.
[light laughter]
I only found out today
why am i so upset
It was just a robot
If you want to come, come, if you want to go, go, if you want to do it, do it.
Concerns or sincerity about the mother
There wasn't even one
You can't learn that
They said they would teach me
It's not like you can know
So of course I didn't know
But our first-year teacher
You already know that, right?
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
Let's leave before it gets stuck
Now, this
(Lee Young) What is this?
You can give it to Mr. Gu Do-won.
Please make sure to tell me within today
[Embarrassed sigh]
yes
(Minha) It’s important for the mother.
Please hurry up, okay?
huh?
yes
[Minha’s light smile]
thank you
[cell phone ringing sound]
Oh, wait a minute.
[Minha’s surprised gasp]
Uh, honey
(Minha) Yes
Kalguksu?
Ah, good
Oh, then add me some extras.
Yeah
[Happy laughter]
Okay, I love you more, yeah
Yeah, okay, yeah
[Call end sound]
Yes, newlyweds
[light laughter]
(Lee Young) Ah
[Minha’s shy laugh]
Well then, goodbye teacher Oh I-young.
- thank you
- (Minha) Hey, what is gratitude?
[Minha’s light laughter]
I did really well today
We'll definitely see you again
(Lee Young) IC
hello
Let's talk
yes
(Jeongmin) I watched
(Sabi) Yes?
Cheon Eun-pyo, mother at MFICU
Ah, yes
sorry
It's nothing to be sorry about
(Jeongmin) Don’t say you can’t do it.
Why not try something else instead?
yes?
(Jae-il) I will work hard!
[Snoring sound is heard]
[Jaeil’s surprised gasp]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
[Sound of head hitting]
[Jaeil groans in pain]
[Snoring sound is heard]
[Sabi’s snoring sound]
Hey there
(Eunpyo) Teacher
It's so noisy that I can't sleep.
sorry
Oh, it's not like I'm protesting, really.
I'll count it as an apology
Go
Hey, that's it.
It's not an apology, I'm worried.
What?
(Safety) Except what Professor Seo Jeong-min can’t do.
He told me to help by doing what I'm good at.
I analyzed the birth chart.
Since the day before yesterday, my blood pressure baseline has been
It seems to be rising little by little
In the morning, my blood pressure was 90 out of 150 for a while.
You also had a headache
In my judgment
I was wondering if I was getting pre-eclampsia.
Yes?
(Sabi) These are convulsions and seizures
I can come
(Eunpyo) No...
If you're that worried, do it in the morning. In the morning.
You can check it in the morning.
no
The blood test results will come out soon.
(Sabi) I was only planning to go after seeing the blood test results.
I usually don't sleep
I just found out that you snore again
(Eunpyo) Oh, that’s it, it’s over.
[Thump sound]
(Mother) Uh, teacher, here!
[nervous music]
(Sabi) Teacher Eunpyo Cheon’s mother collapsed!
Quick, please attach a monitor quickly, quickly!
Wait a minute, get out of the way!
(Lee Young) Teacher, this
(Dowon) Oh, are you here?
(Lee Young) Songdo Yulje Fellow
I told you to give it to me
It's important
He told me to deliver it quickly.
Oh, be sure to call to confirm when you receive it.
(Dowon) Oh, yeah
Oh, that's right, I almost forgot.
thank you
(Lee Young) No, then
(Do-won) Dr. Oh I-young, do you want to go see the surgery?
You haven't seen your twin yet.
(Lee Young) Uh...
[Sound of door opening]
no
Let's go
(Dowon) Okay, go, then
- Are you ready?
- (together) yes
- (Do-won) Please bring the mother with me.
- (Re-elected) Yes
[Sound of door opening]
(Sora) Teacher Oh I-young
- (Lee Young) Hello
- (Sora) Because of you, our teacher Joo Sang-hyeon
Do you know that the professor scolded me so much?
(Lee Young) Yes?
[Sora's sigh]
(Sora) What is General?
What is a general?
(Lee Young) General anesthesia...
(Sora) At General
Full body and lower body anesthesia
You know there are two, right?
But if you just call it general
Is it the whole body or the lower body?
How do we know?
[dark music]
You have to do the notification correctly.
This is basic, basic!
(Lee Young) So far, the lower body
Don't say general
Notified with Spinal
It has been said that only general anesthesia is general.
So I did that too
(Sora) Is it our mistake?
[Sora's snort]
Then what did Noti say then?
Say the same thing
Try again? Let's take a look
(Sanghyun) Teacher
- At that time, I...
- (Sora) No
Don’t remember how you did Noti?
Try again, let me hear it
[Sound of door opening]
(Dowon) Try it, Notty.
You want to try it?
Try notifying it the same way as before.
[Lee Young sighs]
(Lee Young) Mother Rose Hwa
Baby's heart rate is not good
General please
[Sora's snort]
(Dowon) It’s the same, like the note I did today?
What's wrong with me?
I don't know, sir.
(Sora) Yes?
Then...
Why is the preparation wrong?
(Dowon) The current Noti method is
If you are uncomfortable
That's with our professors
I think we need to talk.
It's a word we've all used together like that.
It's not a problem we can solve.
(Sora) No, well...
I don't want to change it
No, if only this teacher joins in.
Because things keep going wrong
It's just for confirmation, or something like that.
Something happened last time too
(Dowon) What happened last time?
What kind of thing are you talking about?
(Sora) I heard it from Sanghyun.
Teacher Oh I-young
I'm going to have a section on my mother's night
You lied and said it was an emergency and got off?
Does that make sense?
(Sanghyun) Teacher, what about that?
(Dowon) No.
The result may have been that way
Teacher Oh I-young lied
I wouldn't have left the operating room.
[Calm music]
Our first year students don't work like that.
I didn't teach you that
It's never happened before
Teacher Myeong-won here will also know this.
(Eunwon) Huh?
Um, I was going to talk about it already.
Something must have gone wrong back then.
sorry
Well, I think everyone is ready.
I have to scrub and come back.
[Sound of door opening]
(Sora) What was there?
(Sanghyun) That’s...
[Sound of door closing]
Teacher Eom Jae-il told me
With teacher Eom Jae-il
When I was with Teacher Oh I-young
Teacher Myung-won Myeong-won
You called me saying it was an emergency.
So, Teacher Oh I-young
It was arranged in a hurry
(Mugang) Yes, I heard that too.
(Sora) Really?
Ah, then...
don't speak
(Sanghyun) I’m sorry
[Sora clears his throat]
(Lee Young) I really didn’t do that.
I'm not that kind of person
(Dowon) Still
Because it is true that I suffered harm to the anesthesiology department.
I apologize again
A misunderstanding like this will never happen again
I won't make it
and
Our first year ahead
I will scold you
[Exciting music]
If you did something wrong
please tell me right away
I will scold you
(Sora) Sure, whatever.
Let's get ready, quickly
(Dowon) Are you going to be there?
(Lee Young) Yes
(Eunpyo) Teacher
[ECG meter beeping sound]
Is the baby okay? There's no problem, right?
(Sabi) Yes
Can I go see the baby?
(Eunpyo) It’s okay
(private money) No.
Ah...
About 6 to 8 hours
I need to calm down.
And I'm dizzy anyway
You won't be able to walk properly.
no
Walking will be difficult.
Teacher too
It's so consistent
yes
(Sabi) Over there
The doctor... said I shouldn't do it.
I tried that
But I really want to become a doctor.
It's the only thing I want to do
Do it!
I'm angry and I'm holding back on what I said
Who am I to block someone's way?
our hope
(Eunpyo) They were originally twins.
I suddenly became an only child at 30 weeks.
(Sabi) Yes, I saw the chart.
Clothes, clothes, stroller
I bought two each
Suddenly there is only one pair left.
(Eunpyo) If someone says they will give it to you,
I think they'll hate it because it's a dead kid.
Throwing it away again
I can't do it
So
I'm planning to have a second child.
[Calm music]
(Sabi) Ah
[Eunpyo’s sigh]
(Eunpyo) The test tube is really
I'm so sick of it just thinking about it.
I'll do it again
teacher
Will you take the second one?
The second one was also a caesarean section.
It's not about receiving, it's about taking out.
[Program operation sound effect]
(Sabi) And the next pregnancy
If it's too close
The incidence of premature birth is rising
Oh, you're apologizing.
[Eunpyo’s painful exclamation]
[Eunpyo’s heavy sigh]
[Painful elasticity]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I apologize, sir.
(Sabi) Ah
[sigh]
[frustrated sigh]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
I also apologize
And for saying that
[Calm music]
thank you
[laughter]
[Jaeil’s sigh]
(Japan) I don’t know if he ran away.
what am i doing here
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Nanjing) Hey!
I'm surprised
Oh, why?
(Nanjing) Where are you and what are you doing?
Don't come quickly, come quickly
Don't you know I can't do it without you?
(Jaeil) Well, can I not exist again?
[upbeat music]
Why? Did you find me, much?
(Namkyung) Oh, that’s it, it pops up in 1 second, quickly.
[Call end sound]
(Dowon) Sir, I received your documents successfully.
Thanks to you, I’ve been here for a year
But how did you know?
(Minha) All the mothers are coming.
I came with such a big backpack
It's my first time seeing you for a year
Dowon, be nice to me, okay?
yes, i understand
(Minha) But that first year.
I saw it for a moment and it looked really good.
I feel like I saw it during my first year at Gudowon.
Hey, I did that?
No way, I did a good job
(Minha) Good luck, I’m hanging up.
yes, thank you
[Call end tone]
be surprised
(Lee Young) Thank you for your hard work
(Dowon) Oh, good job.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
What's wrong?
Go home quickly
yes
What, it hurts, where?
no
Are you saying go home?
yes
(Dowon) Will you come out tomorrow?
You can't run away and do something like that?
Yes, I will go to work tomorrow
Not tomorrow, but always.
I should try more
Where are you going?
don't forget
(Do-won) I owe 5,000 to my in-laws.
See you tomorrow, Oh Iyoung, goodbye.
[Lee Young clears his throat]
[Sound of door opening]
Hey, why are you here now? sit down quickly
(Lee Young) Uh, why, why, what’s wrong?
(Nanjing) There’s work all the time.
Kids
I found a lot, right? You waited so long, right?
[Sound of door closing]
(Sabi) Oh, I completely found it.
Really? why?
Are you asking because you don’t know?
Without you, we can't get off work
(Lee Young) Ah
(Nanjing) Not even one person
Don't even call me
Haha, very vicious, very
Oh, turn notice?
Anyway, you can't do it without me, right?
yes?
- (Lee Young) Ah, then
- (Namkyung) What are you saying?
[cell phone ringing sound]
I'll do it first
[Jaeil clears his throat]
(Jae-il) Yes, teacher
I am a cold radish today
I don't have any patients.
Yes?
What, do you want to do it again?
(Lee Young) What can I do again when I don’t have it?
(Sabi) Don’t you know cold radish?
(Jaeil) Ah, yes, thank you
[Call end tone]
They say we don’t have to notify the turn anymore.
What?
(Residence in Japan) Teachers of higher level
I decided to organize it and report it!
[upbeat music]
Really?
Then
[Cheers from Nanjing]
I'm off work!
(Namkyung) Hey, hey, what are you doing? Change your clothes quickly.
(Jae-il) Quickly, quickly, let’s go
(Dowon) Ah, it’s hot
Why is this so hot?
Because it's hot
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
But to teacher Myeong-won,
What did you say?
Are you saying you don’t receive turn notifications?
(Dahye) Ah, I’m famous for not being able to communicate.
Well...
Give and take?
Should I do that as compensation for pretending not to know?
(Dahye) Yes?
There is such a thing.
(Dahye) [Laughing] Then, I
Can I make Eom Jae-il work starting tomorrow?
I can't back up anymore
Okay, alarm lifted as of today
(Dowon) The kids will be fine for the time being.
(Eunmi) This is all thanks to my rice shuttle.
Even if you want to run away
When people are full, they become positive.
(Dahye) Teacher, let’s sleep.
They say you need to sleep to reset your mood.
To put the teacher in Japan to sleep
I assisted in the surgery and even provided charting.
I'm afraid I'll get hurt again in the ward.
It was really hard not to let me come.
(Dowon) No, no, no, no!
Neither food nor sleep
Do you do business for one or two days?
What don't you know?
(Dowon) Ah, it’s hot!
[Eunmi’s embarrassed groan]
(Eunmi) Are you stupid?
[Eunmi’s laughter]
(Do-won) Today is
Just today
What is it?
salary
(Eunmi) Ah
[Dahye’s empty laughter]
(Dahye) That’s right, somehow
[Eunmi’s laughter]
-I was feeling particularly good today.
- (Eunmi) Yes
[Eunmi and Dahye laugh]
While we're at it, let's go out and eat something.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
I'll shoot, I'll still
Wouldn't you like to earn more than you guys?
[Dahye’s laughter]
(Eunmi) Oh, really?
uh? Let's go
[Eunmi and Dahye laugh]
(Dahye) Ah! Get something expensive
[Dahye’s laughter]
[Nanjing’s happy cheers]
(Namkyung) Hey, you guys came in too, right?
(together) uh
[Lee Young’s irritated breathing]
(Lee Young) No matter how much I earn, it’s negative, I feel bad
(Residing in Japan) When you get your first paycheck
parents
Shouldn’t I buy you underwear?
Sabi Kim, what are you going to do?
(Sabi) What kind of underwear are you wearing these days? Hearttech.
(Nanjing) I’m going to book a summer vacation
I put all this money in
(Japan) Are we on vacation?
(Lee Young) It has to be there
If not, is it a job?
(Japan) Yes
(Lee Young) Ah, I’m hungry
I couldn't eat a single meal today
(Residence in Japan) Huh? To commemorate our first paycheck today
Shall we eat together?
There is a pasta restaurant in front of the hospital.
Are you going to stay up late there?
Isn’t cotton a bit like that at night?
(Sabi) I don’t eat well at night
I eat alone in the evening, I eat alone
- Well, I'll go first.
- (Residing in Japan) Uh
- (Nanjing) See you tomorrow
- (Sabi) Hello
next time
I can eat it next time, okay?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes, teacher
(Dahye) Teacher Eom Jae-il
Well... it's a pasta place in front of our hospital.
-If I didn't eat...
- (Japan) I will go right away.
thank you, teacher
[Call end tone]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Dahye) First-year students have a lot to do, right?
My hands are still a bit slow so it takes a long time.
(Namkyung) Oh, I’m still in my first year.
(Lee Young) I don’t have anything to say right now.
Because you just say you don’t know everything
(Patient 2) How
You don’t know more than the patient.
(Junmo) Hey, is this difficult?
This isn't basic, it's basic!
(Dahye) Even if it’s a little difficult
Paying hard attention, no
Can’t you do that one thing correctly?
It's hard, how can I
How can you not show that it's difficult?
(Lee Young) Is it easy to force yourself to go to the hospital?
(Jooyoung) This bastard, really
(Japan) Book report and thesis report
What are you doing if you just fill your head?
Studying is not everything in practice
(Dowon) Oh, Eomjju!
Me? Are you giving it to me?
(Dowon) Isn’t this the first year of obstetrics and gynecology?
(Jaeil) If you’re not sure, just say this
(Sabi) How easy is it to solve something?
Without even knowing it, Mr.
(Jaeil) Isn’t this great?
(Jeongmin) Where is Gu Dowon?
I can't see the chief.
(Namkyung) I keep looking at you and smiling
What could it be?
It's love